[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The theory of plate tectonics explains the movement of lithospheric plates. Tectonics comes from the Greek word tekton, meaning this.", "correct_answer": "one who constructs", "incorrect_answers": ["one who destroys", "one who floats", "one who moves"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Curlys wife doing to him in the first scene of the movie Chinatown?", "correct_answer": "She was cheating on him/", "incorrect_answers": ["She was poisoning him/", "She was eating his cheesecake/", "She was stealing money/"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What character from the movie Wedding Crashers said,You shut your mouth when your talking to me?", "correct_answer": "Mrs. Kroeger", "incorrect_answers": ["Mrs. Davis", "Mrs. Jones", "Mrs. Cleary"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What job was Butterfly McQueens first goal?", "correct_answer": "nursing", "incorrect_answers": ["political scientist", "ballet dancing", "acting"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Peach trees bloom in beautiful aromatic flowers in this season.", "correct_answer": "Early spring", "incorrect_answers": ["Early fall", "Early summer", "Late summer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Unlike most cats, cheetahs prefer to hunt during the day.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This small shell shaped pasta with slightly rolled-in edges is very popular in the Avellino province of Italy.", "correct_answer": "cavatelli", "incorrect_answers": ["fregula", "orzo", "ditali"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first Peaceful Nuclear Explosion (PNE) blast in the US was conducted in which year?", "correct_answer": "1961", "incorrect_answers": ["1960", "1959", "1965"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the meaning if the word kibbeh which refers to a popular dish in the Arab world and in Brazil?", "correct_answer": "Ball", "incorrect_answers": ["Eye", "Cube", "Ring"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What famous person made the following observation about fashion: Fashion wears out more apparel than the man?", "correct_answer": "Shakespeare", "incorrect_answers": ["Chanel", "Saint Laurent", "Lagerfeld"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor starred in the movies Billy Madison, Happy Gilmore, Big Daddy, Punch-Drunk Love, Spanglish, Click, and Reign Over Me?", "correct_answer": "Adam Sandler", "incorrect_answers": ["Bradley Whitford", "Steve Buscemi", "Darren McGavin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which country has the river Danube as most of its northern border?", "correct_answer": "Bulgaria", "incorrect_answers": ["Austria", "Hungary", "Romania"]}]